Guide to the Ray Lyman Wilbur, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0064A
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- 1917-1918, Series 2
  - Inventories - President's House (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Inventories - President's House (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - President's Reports - correspondence, (1916-17); President's Report, suggestions and corrections (1916-17), 1916-1917 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Psychology; Publications; Publicity - Hoffman (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Ra - Ri; Recommendation of teachers, 1916 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Recommendations, Letters of, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Recommendations, Letters of, 1918 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Registrar; Registration, Committee on, 1917-1940 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Rhodes Scholarship Committee, 1915-1918 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Ro - Ry; Romanic Languages (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Russian; Research (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Sa (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - San Francisco Polyclinic and Post Graduate College (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Sc - Sm; Scholarship Deficiencies (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - School of Education, 1916-17 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - School of Education, 1917-18 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Schools (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Sn - Sy (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Social Service; Special Workers; Stanford Family (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Stanford, Thomas Welton (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Student Adviser, 1916-17 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Student Adviser, 1917-18 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Student Affairs (1916-18); Student Applications for War Service; Student's Guild; Summer Schools, 1916-1918 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Ta - Ti; Teaching Staff; To - Ty (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Townley, S. D.; Trustees (Individual) (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - U, V (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Union High School (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Unique; Visitors (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Wa - Wi; Wo - Wy (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Women's Athletic Association (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - YMCA (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Zoology; X, Y, Z (Box 26, Folder 2)
- 1918-1919, Series 3
  - A (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Associated Students; Alumni; Alumni Secretary (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - American Association of University Professors; Anatomy; Anti-Vivisection (1918) (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Applications for Positions in the University, 1918-1919 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Applications for Positions in the University, 1919 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Applications for Positions in the University, 1919 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Applied Mathematics; Appointments Secretary (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Appointments, 1918-1919 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Appointments, 1919 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Articles of Organization (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Athletics, 1911-1916 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Athletics, 1916-1918 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Athletics, 1918-1919 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Ba; Bacteriology (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Be - Bi; Bequests; Bl - Bu (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Board of Athletic Control; Botany (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Br - By; Botulism (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Botulism (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Budget (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Ca - Cl; California committee on Physical Education (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - California, Univ. Of (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Carnegie Endowment, 1915-1919 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching, 1917-1918 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Carnegie Foundation, 1916 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Carnegie Foundation, 1916-1917 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Carnegie Foundation, 1917-1919 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Chemistry (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Civil Engineering (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Co - Cy (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - D; Dean of Men (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Dean of Women (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Dormitories (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - E (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Economics (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Education (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Electrical Engineering (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - English (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Entomology (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - F; Fellowships (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Fraternities; Ga - Gn (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Geology (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - German; Greek; Go - Gy; Grounds (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - H (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - History (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - History (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Hopkins Marine Station (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - I; J (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Jordan, D. S. (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - K; L (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Latin; Law (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Library (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - M (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Mathematics; Mechanical Engineering (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Medical School, 1918 Aug. - Sept. (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Medical School (1918 Oct.); Medical School (1918 Nov.); Medical School (1918 Dec.), Oct.-Dec. 1918 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Medical School (1919 Jan.); Medical School (1919 Feb.), Jan.-Feb. 1919 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Medical School (1919 Mar.); Medical School (1919 Apr.), Mar.-Apr. 1919 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Medical School (1919 May); Medical School (1919 June), May-June 1919 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Medical School (1919 July); Medical School (1919 Aug.), July-Aug. 1919 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Medical School - Lane Lectures; Memorial Committee (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Memorial Church, 1918 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Memorial Church, 1919 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Military - Camp Fremont; Military - Casualty List of Stanford men (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Military - Essential Teachers (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Military - Students requesting recommendations for Commissions, 1917 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Military - Students requesting recommendations for Commissions, 1918 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Military - Students requesting recommendations for Commissions, 1918 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Military - Students requesting recommendations for Commissions, 1918 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Military - Students requesting recommendations for Commissions, 1919 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Military - Lists of Men - Naval (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Military - ROTC, 1918 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Military - ROTC, 1919 Jan-Feb (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Military - ROTC, 1919 Mar (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Military - ROTC, 1919 Apr-May (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Military - ROTC, 1919 June - July (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Military - Students Army Training Corps (SATC), NO DATE (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Military - Students Army Training Corps (SATC), NO DATE (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Military - SATC, 1918 Aug (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Military - SATC, 1918 Sep (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Military - SATC, 1918 Sept (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Military - SATC, 1918 Oct (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Military - SATC, 1918 Nov (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Military - SATC, 1918 Dec (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Military - SATC Stanford, 1918 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Military - SATC Stanford, 1919 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Military - SATC circulars (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Military - SATC circulars (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Military - SATC Naval Section (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Military - SATC Relations with Washington (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Military - SATC Telegrams sent by Regional Director (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Museum (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - O; P (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Pacific Coast Conference; Philosophy (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Physical Training (Men) (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Physical Training (Women) (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Physics; Physiology (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Political Science; President's House (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Psychology; Publicity (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Q; R (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Recommendations (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Registrar; Rhodes Scholarship Committee (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Romanic Languages; Russian (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - S (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Shedd, Margaret; T (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Trustees (Individuals), 1918-1919 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Trustees (Individuals), 1919 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Tuition; U, V; Unique; Vacation Quarters (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - W (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Women's Club House; X, Y, Z; Zoology (Box 36, Folder 8)
- 1919-1920, Series 4
  - A, 1919 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - A, 1920 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Secretary; Anatomy (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Applications for Positions, 1919-1920 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Applications for Positions, 1920 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Applied Mathematics; Appointment Secretary; Arboretum; Arrangement of Departments in existing Buildings (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Assistants - Departmental (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Assistants - Departmental (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Associated Students; Athletics for Women (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - B, 1919-1920 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - B, 1920 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Bacteriology (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Blodgett, D. P. (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Board of Athletic Control (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Botany (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Budget (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - C (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - C (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - California Board of Education (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Chaparral; Chemistry (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - California, University of (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Civil Engineering; Commencement (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Comptroller (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Comptroller (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - D; Daily Palo Alto (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Dean of Men; Dean of Women (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Dormitories; E (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Economics; Education (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Electrical Engineering; Encina Hall (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - English (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Entomology (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - F (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Fellowships (C.R.B.) (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Fraternities; Funk, P. K. (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - G (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - General Biology (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Geology (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - German; Greek (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - H (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Hewston, J. E. (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - History (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Hopkins Marine Station; Housing Problem (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - I; J (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Jordan, David Starr; Journalism; Junior College (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - K (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - L (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Latin; Law (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Library (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - M (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Mathematics; Mechanical Engineering; Mining (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Medical School (1919 Sept.); Medical School (1919 Oct.), Sept.-Oct. 1919 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Medical School (1919 Nov.); Medical School (1919 Dec.), Nov.-Dec. 1919 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Medical School (1920 Jan.); Medical School (1920 Feb.), Jan.-Feb. 1920 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Medical School (1920 Mar.); Medical School (1920 Apr.), Mar.-Apr. 1920 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Medical School (1920 May); Medical School (1920 June), May-June 1920 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Medical School, 1920 July (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Medical School, 1920 Aug. (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Medical School - Lane Medical Lectures; Medical School - Auxiliary to Stanford Clinics (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Memorial Church (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Men's Conference and Council (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Military Training (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Mining and metallurgy; Museum (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - N (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - National Research Council (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - O (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - P (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Pensions; Philosophy (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Physical Training - Men (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Physical Training - Women (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Physics, 1919 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Physics, 1920 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Physiology; Political Science (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Psychology; Publicity (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Q; R (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Recommendations, letters of (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Registrar (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Reorganization of Undergraduate Education; Research (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Rhodes Scholarship (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Romanic Languages; Russian (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - S (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - S (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Salaries (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Shedd, Margaret; Six, Committee of (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Sloss, Leon - Business Manager and Treasurer; Social Service Board (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Home for Convalescent Children; Stanford Illustrated Review (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Stanford, Thomas Welton, Estate of; Student's Guild (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Sword and Sandals (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - T (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Trustees, Individual (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Tuition fee; U (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Unique; University Press (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - V (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - W (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - War Service Committee; War - Stanford Correspondence (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Stanford War History - a chronology (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - War Service Memorial, 1919 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - War Work for Women, 1918 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - War Effort and Students, 1917-1918 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Dormitories (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - War Effort Participation by YMCA and Others (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Water Supply; Y; YMCA and YWCA; Women's Athletic Association; Women's Conference and Council (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Z; Zoology (Box 45, Folder 3)
- 1920-1921, Series 5
  - A (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Admissions; Alumni Secretary (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Anatomy (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Applications for Positions (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Applications for Positions (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Applied Mathematics; Appointment Secretary (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Appointment Secretary; Assistants (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Assistants; Associated Students (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - B (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - B (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Bacteriology (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Bequests to the Univ.; Blodgett, D. P.; Board of Athletic Control (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Botany (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - C (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - California, University Of (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - California, University Of (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Canfield Foundation (Psychology) (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Canfield Foundation (Psychology) (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Carnegie Foundation (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Chemistry; Civil Engineering (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Class of '96 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Commencement (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Comptroller (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Comptroller (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - D; Daily Palo Alto (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Dean of Women (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Dean of Women (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Dean of Women (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Dean of Women; Dean of Men; Dormitories; E (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Education (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Education (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Economics; Electrical Engineering (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Electrical Engineering; Encina Hall; English (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - English (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Endowment Fund (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Endowment Fund (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Endowment Fund (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Endowment Fund (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Endowment Fund (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Endowment Fund (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Endowment Fund (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Endowment Fund (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - F (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Club; Faculty Housing; Faculty Tuitions (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Fellowships, C.R.B. (French Universities) (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Fellowships, C.R.B. (French Universities) (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Financial Condition (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Food Research Institute (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Food Research Institute (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Food Research Institute (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Fraternities (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - G; General Biology (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - General Biology (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Geology (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - German; Greek; H (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - H (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - History (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Hopkins Marine Station; Housing Problems (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - I; J (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Jordan, David Starr (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Junior College; K (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - L; Latin (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Law (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Library (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Limitation of Students; M (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - M; Mathematics (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Mechanical Engineering (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Medical School, 1920 Sept. - Dec. (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Medical School, 1920 Sept. - Dec. (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Medical School, 1920 Sept. - Dec. (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Medical School, 1921 Jan. - Apr. (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Medical School, 1921 Jan. - Apr. (Box 51, Folder 5)
- 1921-1922, Series 6
  - Applied Mathematics; Appointments Secretary; Associated Students (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Assistants, 1922-23 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Assistants, 1922-23 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Assistants, 1922-23 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - B (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - B (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Bacteriology; Biology; Blodgett, D. P. (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Board of Athletic Control (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Board of Athletic Control (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Botany (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - C (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - California, University Of; Carnegie Foundation (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Carnegie Foundation; Chaparral; Chemistry (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Civil Engineering; Commencement; Comptroller (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Comptroller (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Comptroller (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - D; Daily Palo Alto (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Dean of Men; Dean of Women (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - E (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Economics (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Education (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Education (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Electrical Engineering (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - English; F (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - F; Fellowships, C.R.B. and Foreign (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Fellowships, C.R.B. and Foreign; Faculty Club House; Faculty Housing (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Food Research Institute (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Fraternities (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - G; General Biology (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - General Education Board; Geology (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - German; Greek (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - H (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - History (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - History; Hopkins Marine Station (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - I; J (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - K (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - K; L (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Latin; Law (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Library (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - M (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - M (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Mathematics; Mechanical Engineering (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Medical School (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Medical School (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Medical School (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Medical School (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Medical School (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Medical School (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Lane Medical Lectures; Medical Society, State of California (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Memorial Church; Men's Conference and Council (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Military Training (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Military Training (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Military Training (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Mimeo and Steno Charges; Mining and Metallurgy (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Museum; N (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - N (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - O; P (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - P (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - P; Palo Alto Hospital (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Palo Alto Hospital; Philosophy; Physical Education, Encina (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Physical Education, Encina (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Physical Education, Encina (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Physical Education, Encina; Physical Education, Roble (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Physics; Physiology (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Political Science; Post Office; Psychology (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Psychology (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Psychology; Publicity (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Q, R (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - R; Recommendations, Letters of; Registrar (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Rhodes Scholarships (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Romanic Languages; Russian (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - S (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - S (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Sororities; Stadium; Stanford Clinics Auxiliary; Stanford Dramatic Council; Stanford Home for Convalescent Children; Stanford Medal (Mexico); Stanford War Service Memorial (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Student Publications; Student's Guild (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Summer Quarter, 1922 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Trustees, Individual (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - U, general (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Unique, V, and W (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - W (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Women's Conference and Council (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Y; YMCA and YWCA; Z; Zoology (Box 57, Folder 13)
- 1922-1923, Series 7
  - A, general, 1922 Sept. - Dec. (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - A, general, 1923 Jan. - Aug. (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Secretary (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Anatomy (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Applications for Positions, 1922 Sept. - 1923 Mar. (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Applications for Positions, 1923 Apr. - May (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Applications for Positions, 1923 June - Aug. (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Applied Mathematics (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Appointments Secretary (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Assistants, non-academic (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Assistants, academic departments A - E (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Assistants, academic departments F - M (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Assistants, academic departments P - R (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Associated Students (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - B, general (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - B, general (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - B, general (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Bacteriology (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Bequests to the Univ. (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Blodgett, D. P. (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Board of Athletic Control (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Botany (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Branner Memorial Association (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - C, general (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - C, general (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - C, general (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Carnegie Foundation (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - California, University Of, 1922 Sept. - Dec. (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - California, University Of, 1923 Jan. - Aug. (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Chaparral (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Chemistry (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Citizenship (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Civil Engineering (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Classical Literature (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Commencement (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Comptroller, 1922 Sept. - 1923 Jan. (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Comptroller, 1923 Jan. - June (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Comptroller, 1923 May - Aug. (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - D, general (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Daily Palo Alto (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Dean of Men (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Dean of Women (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Dormitories (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - E, general (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Eating Clubs (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Economics (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Education (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Electrical Engineering (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Military Science and Tactics (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Military Science and Tactics (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Endowment (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Endowment (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Endowment (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - English (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - F, general (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Fellowships, C.R.B. and Foreign (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Fellowships, C.R.B. and Foreign (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Food Research Institute (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Fraternities (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - G, general (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - General Education Board (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Geology (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - German (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - H, general (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - H, general (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - History (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Hopkins Marine Station (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - I, general (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - J, general (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - K, general (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - L, general (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Lane medical Lectures (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Law (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Library (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - M, general (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - M, general (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Mathematics (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Mechanical Engineering (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Medical School (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Medical School (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Medical School (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Medical School (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Medical School (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Memorial Church (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Men's Conference and Council (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Mining and Metallurgy (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Museum (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - N, general (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - O, general (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - P, general (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Palo Alto Hospital (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Philosophy (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Physical Education: Encina (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Physical Education: Roble (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Physics (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Physiology (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Political Science (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Psychology: Gifted Children Project (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Psychology: Gifted Children Project (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Publicity (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - R, general (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - R, general (Box 65, Folder 5)